guess
how much i love you
colors
red
purple
green
blue
pink
orange
oh yellow hello
my name is little nut brown hair what's
yours
your name is quack
was that a yes or a no
oh
then what kind of animal are you
you can't be a hare because you haven't
got long ears like me
i wonder what you are
well it was very nice to meet you little
yellow
thing
bye
oh
you're following me
[Music]
i guess you are
all right can you do this
[Music]
but what about this
you didn't copy my jump backwards well
thanks for the game
would you like to come and visit my
friend littlefield mouse with me
follow me
[Music]
he follows you everywhere everywhere he
followed me all the way to visit you
littlefield mouse
hello
what's your name
that's all he ever says i think he's too
young to talk
oh
hmm
do you know what he is
i know he isn't a hare
hmm
well i think he's uh
oh i know he's probably
oh
well whatever he is he can't be a mouse
because he doesn't have whiskers like me
we can't call him whatever he is he
needs a proper name i know i know we can
call him
little
yes yellow
uh-huh
[Music]
i don't know
you've got to have a name
everyone does
that's it what we'll call him little
yellow quack yay perfect
what do you think of that
little yellow quack
[Music]
hmm i see
well i've looked at little yellow quack
from every side and
and i'm sure that he is
a squirrel a swirl
a yellow quacking squirrel can't you see
we could be brothers huh oh
what haha just jerking
a quacking squirrel quack
i've no idea why little yellow quack
lives
but i do know he is not a fox
is it his color well yes but
is it his tail that too
but but what little redwood fox
he can't be a fox because foxes don't
have wings
wings
you're not being tricky are you little
redwood fox
me
well not this time
[Music]
they are wings very little wings birds
have wings little yellow quack could be
some kind of bird a bird
what's happened to little yellow quack
look there he is in the river
[Music]
wow
he can swim really well
no
he's over there
no look
oh
huh
[Music]
now there's three
a big brown duck
she must be little yellow crack's mother
little yellow quack looks so different
to big brown duck
not even the same color
hey
little yellow quack is really little
yellow
dark
[Music]
yellow